<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trevor Idayaa Kevin Xavier</title>
    <link>https://txavier1998.github.io/website/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Trevor Idayaa Kevin Xavier</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://txavier1998.github.io/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://txavier1998.github.io/website/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 16:02:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://txavier1998.github.io/website/projects/</guid>
      <description>Predicting 3 Pointer Accuracy for NBA Players  Scraped 10 years’ worth of NBA shooting statistics and Implemented data pre-processing and feature engineering such as standardization and one-hot encoding to reduce potential for overfitting Employed regression, classification and ensemble methods through bagging models such as Random Forest on features to predict 3 point percentage. Selected best hyperparameters by finetuning the number of learners and nodes per decision tree Employed neural net using Adams optimizer through TensorFlow to reduce the loss function mean squared error of the regression model by 18% and misclassification rate by 12% Finalized that best contributors to a better three point percentage were the players’ Free Throw percentage and offensive rating based on models developed  Link: https://drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://txavier1998.github.io/website/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://txavier1998.github.io/website/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone, welcome to my website. My name is Trevor Idayaa Kevin Xavier and I was born in Dubai on March 27th 1998. I did my undergrad in Aerospace Engineering at Embry-Riddle Aeronautical University with a concentration in Aeronautics. Currently I am a masters student majoring in Operations Research and Information Engineering with a concentration in Applied Operations Research.
This website provides access to my resume and past projects that I have worked on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
